

Candidature of: (Mr.) Arvinder Singh Narula (ナルラ)

Curriculum Vitae

Objective

I have a strong desire to work at an internationally challenging position and in a multicultural work environment.

With 8 years of experience in the Japanese corporate world and ability of Japanese language skills – I wish to work with a corporate that has global business standards.

Current Employment:

Manager with Alue India Pvt. Ltd. – Japanese MNC at Gurgaon since 15th September 2014.

At Alue India – my core profile is to manage and execute projects for Japanese corporate clients from different industries like automobile, pharmaceutical, construction, food, insurance etc.

- a) Global communication with Japanese staff and clients
- b) International coordination
- c) Japanese Expat Management
- d) Projects Execution as per directives of Tokyo HO
- e) General Affairs
- f) Administrative & Accounting
- g) Bridge between Japanese and Indian management and resources
- h) Support to Japanese management and Japanese clients
- i) Japanese English Translation
- j) Travel as and when required
- k) Facilities management

Current CTC: Rs. 16.80 Lac per annum

Past Employment:

Hirohama India Private Ltd. ("HIP") (a Japanese entity in India) Gurgaon, Haryana (Designation - Deputy General Manager)

At HIP my core role was to provide and manage various business support services to various Japanese corporate to set up business in India and be able to work smoothly by providing a 'Japan Like' environment

Tenure: 5 years and 6 months (01st April 2009 – 13th September 2014)

The job role included the following:

- a) General Affairs and Administrative Duties
- b) Japanese Expat Management
- c) Business Support Services to Japanese client companies in Delhi NCR and Japanese Industrial Zone at Neemrana
- d) Real Estate Management running the properties of the company successfully in Gurgaon and Neemrana
- e) Real Estate service for MNCs (Residential & Commercial Space) including marketing, negotiation, contracts formation, registration
- f) Business Development and Revenue Generation
- g) Operation Management and Financial Control
- h) Corporate Rental Car Fleet service complete management
- i) Making company policies, staffing and resource allocation

(June 2005 – December 2006)

FormulaOne Corporate Solutions Private Ltd., Delhi (Designation - Administration Officer)
Posted at the General Affairs Department of the Mitsui & Co. India Pvt. Ltd. Head Office, Delhi

Job roles included the following:

- -General administration
- -Fleet management
- -Bills processing

- -Communication and co-ordination between various branches and departments
- -Vendor management
- -Preparation of the salaries of general staff
- -Residence management of the Japanese staff members
- -Preparation of budgets
- -Management of general affairs of the Japanese staff members

Educational Qualification

#Graduation from Delhi University;2003 (Subjects: Economics, History, English, Hindi)

#Japanese Language study from Department of Chinese and Japanese Studies, (Now called Department of East Asian Studies) Arts Faculty, Delhi University; Year 2000-2004

Two Year (Part Time) Diploma in Japanese, Year 2000-02 One Year Advance Diploma in Japanese, Year 2002-03 One Year Post Intensive Advance Diploma in Japanese, Year 2003-04

#Japanese Language Course at A.C.C. International Culture College, Fujinomiya, Shizuoka-ken, Japan

Duration: January 2007 - March 2008

'Goodwill Ambassador' certification by A.C.C.International Culture College (Shizuoka, Japan).

Certification

- a) Japanese Language Proficiency Level 2
- b) TOEIC score 955

Internship

Internship at Nippon Express Pvt. Ltd. Head Office in Tokyo and also at various locations in and around Tokyo (September – November 2008) on:

- a) Air Logistics
- b) Sea Logistics
- c) Warehouse management
- d) Packaging and dispatch
- e) Customs clearance, rules and procedures
- f) Sales and marketing
- g) Sea port operations
- h) Container yard operations
- i) Airport operations
- j) Trucking management
- k) Drivers training

- I) Delivery management
- m) IT infrastructure
- n) Relocation services

** Basically I have lived in Japan for almost 2 Years

Personal Details

Nationality: Indian

Date of Birth: 07 November 1982 (Age 32 years)

Marital Status: Married

Residential Address: Flat Number 13, Pocket 1,

DDA SFS Flats (Near Manish Mall) Sector – 22, Dwarka, Delhi, INDIA

Mobile Number: +91 9717-548-578

Passport Number: N0574463

E-mail: arvinder117@gmail.com

(Arvinder Singh Narula)